,header,comments,entities_labels
0,How to watch the MLB Postseason 2018,"One edit. TBS will have the AL playoffs after the WED Wildcard game on ESPN.  TBS seems to be a basic channel on all services.  FS1 is exclusive for the NL. MLB Network will mix in some games for both the AL and NL divisional series, mostly day games.Another option is the MLB audio At Bat. It gets audio through your browser and their app. It's a good way if your team is playing a lot of day games while at work.  I think they have an Oct package that is only about $5.00.","[('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('TBS', 'ORG'), ('AL', 'PERSON'), ('WED Wildcard', 'PERSON'), ('ESPN', 'ORG'), ('TBS', 'ORG'), ('NL', 'ORG'), ('MLB Network', 'ORG'), ('AL', 'GPE'), ('NL', 'ORG'), ('day', 'DATE'), ('MLB', 'ORG'), ('Bat', 'PERSON'), ('about $5.00', 'MONEY')]"
1,How to watch the MLB Postseason 2018,I'm stuck in a hotel IN Atlanta with no MLBN on their cable. So weird I can't even watch the Braves in their hometown. ,"[('Atlanta', 'GPE'), ('Braves', 'ORG')]"
2,How to watch the MLB Postseason 2018,Go pick up a FireStick and do a trail of PSVue. ,"[('FireStick', 'ORG'), ('PSVue', 'ORG')]"
3,Netflix is planning a sci-fi universe based on the novel 'Recursion',Will it be self referential? ,[]
4,Netflix is planning a sci-fi universe based on the novel 'Recursion',"Yeah, Netflix is planning a sci-fi universe based on the novel 'Recursion'.","[('Netflix', 'PERSON'), ('Recursion', 'PERSON')]"
5,Netflix is planning a sci-fi universe based on the novel 'Recursion',"I don't know about this, but have any of you seen ""The Expanse""? I read the first book and didn't think too much of it, but when I saw the first season .... great Googly Moogly! Fantastic story that just keeps getting better; not a space soap opera like too many series in the past. ","[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('the first season', 'DATE')]"
6,Netflix is planning a sci-fi universe based on the novel 'Recursion',"The books are fantastic if you keep going with them, the really flesh out the story with details you kind of miss in the show.",[]
7,Netflix is planning a sci-fi universe based on the novel 'Recursion',One that isn't even out yet.  Nice and cheap.  Wayward pines was so dumb though so I'm a little hopeful they don't bring in the original author.,"[('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('Wayward', 'FAC')]"
8,Netflix is planning a sci-fi universe based on the novel 'Recursion',Blake Crouch is a brilliant author. It’s NOT his fault the wayward pines tv series sucked. It loosely (at best) followed the story line of the 3 books.,"[('Blake Crouch', 'PERSON'), ('3', 'CARDINAL')]"
9,Netflix is planning a sci-fi universe based on the novel 'Recursion',"I wonder if this is really the best way to do this - base it on the universe, but not the book. That way there's no ""the book was better"" or ""they're changing the book"". I'd like to see that space explored more.",[]
10,Netflix is planning a sci-fi universe based on the novel 'Recursion',"At the bottom of the article, we get to learn watch the Ellen Pao movie and learn about her trials and tribulations about not getting promoted at her venture fund.  Its going to be great watching the heroic Pao versus the evil more capable venture capitalists who thwart her.","[('Ellen Pao', 'PERSON'), ('Pao', 'PRODUCT')]"
11,Hulu $5.99 deal (for existing subscribers on the same deal),What's the Hulu $5.99 deal?,"[('Hulu', 'GPE'), ('5.99', 'MONEY')]"
12,Hulu $5.99 deal (for existing subscribers on the same deal),You should either have an email or just sign up on the website before the offer expires (I think it's this month?). It's basic Hulu for $5.99 instead of $7.99. I've been on the same plan for years and my rate has always been discounted. ,"[('this month', 'DATE'), ('Hulu', 'GPE'), ('5.99', 'MONEY'), ('7.99', 'MONEY'), ('years', 'DATE')]"
13,Hulu $5.99 deal (for existing subscribers on the same deal),Where do you get the deal?,[]
14,Hulu $5.99 deal (for existing subscribers on the same deal),Cancel and within a month or so you'll get the offer.  I'm in the same boat as OP.,"[('a month', 'DATE'), ('OP', 'GPE')]"
15,Hulu $5.99 deal (for existing subscribers on the same deal),"If you view [the Hulu homepage](https://www.hulu.com/welcome) without logging in, you should see the $5.99 for 1 year offer near the center of the page. ","[('the Hulu homepage](https://www.hulu.com', 'LAW'), ('5.99', 'MONEY'), ('1 year', 'DATE')]"
16,Hulu $5.99 deal (for existing subscribers on the same deal),"Does anyone know if Hulu tv includes the tv show  and commercial free show premium Hulu has? I would like to have live tv with Hulu, since YouTube tv had shows on demand you can’t fast forward. ","[('Hulu', 'GPE'), (' ', 'NORP'), ('Hulu', 'GPE'), ('Hulu', 'GPE'), ('YouTube', 'ORG')]"
17,Hulu $5.99 deal (for existing subscribers on the same deal),"Yes, if you get ""Enhanced Cloud DVR"" you can fast forward your recorded show commercials...except on a couple very strict channels (I've only run into it once or twice - I believe on a sporting event, but most NFL and ESPN games I've been able to fast forward) If you're viewing it direct from their on-demand library, which usually has the most recent few shows and in some cases the whole series, then it doesn't show a commercial at all.Here's how my account is setup:Hulu (No Commercials) with Live TV 43.99/moEnhanced Cloud DVR 14.99/moUnlimited Screens 14.99/mo\-10.00 for bundling the two add-ons aboveHBO 14.99/moShowtime 8.99/moGrand total of 87.95/moThe on-demand library is pretty extensive, and even though the Viacom channels are missing, and BBC America is missing, I'm pretty happy with the channel selection and for getting ALL the local channels and the regional sports channels.You get used to the UI...and my only complaint initially was buffering on live feeds but they've seem to have fixed that and it runs great on 100meg fiber with Roku.","[('NFL', 'ORG'), ('ESPN', 'ORG'), ('Hulu', 'GPE'), ('Live TV', 'ORG'), ('Cloud', 'PERSON'), ('Screens 14.99/mo\\-10.00', 'PERSON'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('aboveHBO', 'PERSON'), ('87.95/moThe', 'CARDINAL'), ('Viacom', 'ORG'), ('BBC America', 'ORG'), ('100meg', 'CARDINAL'), ('Roku', 'PERSON')]"
18,Hulu $5.99 deal (for existing subscribers on the same deal),"It includes the basic Hulu, and I think you can pay $4 extra a month for commercial free Hulu.  If you want to fast forward through commercials on DVR, though, that costs $15 a month.","[('Hulu', 'GPE'), ('$4 extra', 'MONEY'), ('Hulu', 'GPE'), ('DVR', 'ORG'), ('15', 'MONEY')]"
19,Hulu $5.99 deal (for existing subscribers on the same deal),Are you A Ted Danson or THE Ted Danson?,"[('Ted Danson', 'PERSON'), ('THE Ted Danson', 'TIME')]"
20,Hulu $5.99 deal (for existing subscribers on the same deal),THE Ted Danson. AMA!,"[('Ted Danson', 'PERSON'), ('AMA', 'ORG')]"
21,Hulu $5.99 deal (for existing subscribers on the same deal),I switched to commercial free last night. I think it's $12/mo which is $6/mo more for no ads.  But I did some math...  An hour long show on Hulu has about 18min of ads. If you only watch 3 hours of Hulu each month that's almost an hour worth of ads. Would you watch an hour of ads for $6?  That's less than minimum wage.,"[('last night', 'TIME'), ('12/mo', 'MONEY'), ('6/mo', 'MONEY'), ('Hulu', 'GPE'), ('about 18min', 'DATE'), ('3 hours', 'TIME'), ('Hulu', 'GPE'), ('each month', 'DATE'), ('almost an hour', 'TIME'), ('an hour', 'TIME'), ('6', 'MONEY')]"
22,Hulu $5.99 deal (for existing subscribers on the same deal),"Only if you actually sit there and watch the ads. They give you a timer so you know exactly how long you have to pee, grab food, talk, check your phone, etc. I understand why people hate ads and prefer the ad free sub but they don't bother me enough to pay the extra $6. I think I'm in the minority though.","[('6', 'MONEY')]"
23,Hulu $5.99 deal (for existing subscribers on the same deal),Did you have to cancel your subscription to get it? Mine makes me manage through iTunes and didn't have an option for 5. 99.,"[('iTunes', 'GPE'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('99', 'CARDINAL')]"
24,Hulu $5.99 deal (for existing subscribers on the same deal),It may not be available through iTunes. Sign up via the website instead.,"[('iTunes', 'GPE')]"
25,Hulu $5.99 deal (for existing subscribers on the same deal),Is this just a glitch in your favor?It clearly states that it's only for one year then reverts to $7.99 again.,"[('favor?It', 'DATE'), ('one year', 'DATE'), ('7.99', 'MONEY')]"
26,Hulu $5.99 deal (for existing subscribers on the same deal),No. I have this deal too. I received an email about a month ago telling it had been renewed. Its possible that it is targeted to long time Hulu users. I have subscribed repeatedly since the first plan was introduced. I think they are trying to limit churn.,"[('about a month ago', 'DATE'), ('Hulu', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
27,Hulu $5.99 deal (for existing subscribers on the same deal),Mine has already been credited for over a year and is currently showing it will expire Oct 2019.,"[('over a year', 'DATE'), ('Oct 2019', 'DATE')]"
28,Hulu $5.99 deal (for existing subscribers on the same deal),"If you cancel then re-subscribe, do you lose all of your show subscriptions, or do they retain those in case you come back?",[]
29,Hulu $5.99 deal (for existing subscribers on the same deal),"They stick around as long as you're using the same credentials to sign back up as you did the first time. I stopped using Hulu for over a year and came back, and when I did, it still remembered what I was watching from before I left.","[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Hulu', 'GPE')]"
30,Hulu $5.99 deal (for existing subscribers on the same deal),"Man I really wish Hulu would offer any deals or bundles that include the No-Commercials option. I currently subscribe to Hulu through the Hulu/Spotify Premium deal (non-student one), and on one hand it's nice to be able to listen to stuff on Spotify without ever hearing the ultra-annoying ads that you get with Spotify free, but on the other hand it's soooo obnoxious to have to watch ads on Hulu. I don't mind paying more, just give me the option. Hulu especially irritates me with their ads because I routinely watch it between multiple (about 5) devices (TVs with Hulu Apps, Monitors w/ Chromecasts attached, XB1) plus my Android tablet, depending on where I am in the house, and what I'm doing. Every time I stop something I'm watching on Hulu to switch the screen or device I'm using it on, when I resume playback of whatever I was watching, it's been ""rewinded"" back past the most recent ad break so that I'm forced to watch ads again before getting back to where I actually left off. Sometimes I can catch this fast enough to fast forward past the ad break, but usually they still wind up playing. It's infuriating.      ","[('Hulu', 'GPE'), ('Hulu', 'GPE'), ('the Hulu/Spotify Premium', 'GPE'), ('Spotify', 'PERSON'), ('Spotify', 'PERSON'), ('Hulu', 'GPE'), ('Hulu', 'PERSON'), ('about 5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hulu Apps', 'PERSON'), ('Chromecasts', 'ORG'), ('XB1', 'PERSON'), ('Android', 'GPE'), ('Hulu', 'GPE')]"
31,Hulu $5.99 deal (for existing subscribers on the same deal),"Same here for the past 2 years, hopefully I will still have it next month when my $5.99 deal runs out.","[('the past 2 years', 'DATE'), ('next month', 'DATE'), ('5.99', 'MONEY')]"
32,Hulu $5.99 deal (for existing subscribers on the same deal),"Just tried contacting them see if they’d give me the deal, they told me I had to cancel and sign up with a new email. And then was like you’d only save 2 bucks...","[('2 bucks', 'MONEY')]"
33,Hulu $5.99 deal (for existing subscribers on the same deal),You should not need to sign up with a new email. 2 bucks is 2 bucks.,"[('2 bucks', 'MONEY'), ('2 bucks', 'MONEY')]"
34,Hulu $5.99 deal (for existing subscribers on the same deal),It's two buck a month. That's 24 bucks!,"[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('24 bucks', 'MONEY')]"
35,Hulu $5.99 deal (for existing subscribers on the same deal),"It's $24 a year, and is the difference for me between me dropping Hulu or keeping it. I like it much better at $5.99 than $7.99. For $7.99 I'll drop it and pick it up occasionally. For $5.99 it's 'what the heck, I'll just keep it'. Hulu knows this :)","[('24', 'MONEY'), ('Hulu', 'GPE'), ('5.99', 'MONEY'), ('7.99', 'MONEY'), ('7.99', 'MONEY'), ('5.99', 'MONEY'), ('Hulu', 'GPE')]"
37,Philo launches Profiles,Has a guide been added yet?  It's what stopped me cold on Philo for Roku.,"[('Philo', 'GPE'), ('Roku', 'GPE')]"
38,Philo launches Profiles,Yes. https://www.reddit.com/r/PhiloTV/comments/9kw3ea/_/?st=JMWFW9UU&sh=bf99c65a,[]
39,Free TV service Pluto TV lands on Roku streaming players in the UK,"Been using Pluto TV on my android box for a year or so and I really enjoy the service. Programing quality has become much better in the last few months. There are shows, music, movies but nothing that is super recent (except for the music). Honestly my favorite part is that all the channels are uncensored. ","[('year', 'DATE'), ('the last few months', 'DATE')]"
40,Free TV service Pluto TV lands on Roku streaming players in the UK,Let's face it. You just watch cats 24/7,"[('24/7', 'CARDINAL')]"
41,Free TV service Pluto TV lands on Roku streaming players in the UK,On the pro wrestling front they have been adding week old Impact Wrestling episodes.,"[('week', 'DATE'), ('Wrestling', 'GPE')]"
42,Free TV service Pluto TV lands on Roku streaming players in the UK,I'd say bake it on low heat (Around 350 F) for around 35 - 40 minutes. Mine usually ends up crispy on the outside but the flavor is still there. Put some hot sauce on it to add a zip!!,"[('around 35 - 40 minutes', 'TIME')]"
43,Free TV service Pluto TV lands on Roku streaming players in the UK,r/lostredditors,[]
44,Free TV service Pluto TV lands on Roku streaming players in the UK,Don't bake your Roku.,"[('Roku', 'GPE')]"
45,Free TV service Pluto TV lands on Roku streaming players in the UK,Dat zip doe.,[]
46,Free TV service Pluto TV lands on Roku streaming players in the UK,Don't you want to brighten it with some lemon? ,[]
47,Free TV service Pluto TV lands on Roku streaming players in the UK,I watch that damn train channel all the time since putting Pluto TV on my Roku. ,[]
48,Free TV service Pluto TV lands on Roku streaming players in the UK,My 2 year old son loves that channel. He's gets upset when they have to stop though lol,"[('2 year old', 'DATE')]"
49,Free TV service Pluto TV lands on Roku streaming players in the UK,So this just landed for PS4 as well. Is it worth the download to check it out? Seeing quite a bit of mixed reviews. ,"[('PS4', 'PERSON')]"
50,Free TV service Pluto TV lands on Roku streaming players in the UK,"It's good for what it is, they have stadium tv (a free ESPN like channel) plus the 24/7 Mystery science theater 3000 channel is my go to. They also show some decent, abiet older movies. ","[('ESPN', 'ORG'), ('24/7', 'CARDINAL'), ('3000', 'CARDINAL')]"
51,Free TV service Pluto TV lands on Roku streaming players in the UK,"It's been on my TV for a while. It's hit and miss -- mostly low quality content, I would say? But there are some things worth watching for sure. It's basically a free IPTV service, with all that entails.",[]
52,Free TV service Pluto TV lands on Roku streaming players in the UK,"its good to see it expanding. i have been accessing the us version. interestingly if you access the pluto tv website here in australia without trying to circumvent geo blocking, we get a version of live channels made up with strictly youtube videos. it has been these way for like 2 years so im not sure if that means they plan to expand here at some point or not.","[('like 2 years', 'DATE')]"
53,Free TV service Pluto TV lands on Roku streaming players in the UK,Really don't care for this service. It has been slow and clunky on my Roku and desktop. It took them three or four years to support closed captioning even they were required to by law (about the only FCC regulations for streaming services are for closed captioning) even though they got at least three rounds of venture capital funding during that time. Some devices seem to have closed captioning on some channels now but it's inconsistent.,"[('three or four years', 'DATE'), ('FCC', 'ORG'), ('at least three', 'CARDINAL')]"
54,Free TV service Pluto TV lands on Roku streaming players in the UK,"It's been my go to free service lately for background streaming. The Roku performance has picked up from early in the year, at least on my TCL and Roku 3. My understanding (and I may be wrong) is that they are curating the streams of many channels from the content owners, and this is why there is a inconsistency on the CC. ","[('Roku', 'PERSON'), ('the year', 'DATE'), ('TCL', 'ORG'), ('CC', 'ORG')]"
55,Free TV service Pluto TV lands on Roku streaming players in the UK,"About closed captioning, the FCC needs to know this. Tell them at https://consumercomplaints.fcc.gov","[('FCC', 'ORG')]"
56,Free TV service Pluto TV lands on Roku streaming players in the UK,"While I don't really need it to stream MST3K at all times, could somebody tell me where the search function for their on demand titles is?",[]
57,Free TV service Pluto TV lands on Roku streaming players in the UK,My girlfriend and I love the FailArmy channel. just wish they would have did it more often. PlutoTV is the best,"[('FailArmy', 'ORG')]"
58,Free TV service Pluto TV lands on Roku streaming players in the UK,"Didn't see it on the pc version but, on the android tv console there's on demand movies. Hundreds of them. Good ones. ","[('Hundreds', 'CARDINAL')]"
59,Free TV service Pluto TV lands on Roku streaming players in the UK,"Been watching Pluto on my Roku for the last 6 months or so.  If you dig around a little, you always find something of interest - or a good laugh.","[('the last 6 months or so', 'DATE'), (' ', 'ORG')]"
60,Free TV service Pluto TV lands on Roku streaming players in the UK,It's free but you get what you pay for...,[]
61,Free TV service Pluto TV lands on Roku streaming players in the UK,"People TV is a fun one, keeps my gossip junkie happy.","[('People TV', 'ORG')]"
62,Free TV service Pluto TV lands on Roku streaming players in the UK,My only gripe is the far to frequent commercials. It's worse than cable. ,[]
63,Free TV service Pluto TV lands on Roku streaming players in the UK,What gets me is that they play the same commercial exactly 4 times in a row during a single commercial break,"[('4', 'CARDINAL')]"
64,Free TV service Pluto TV lands on Roku streaming players in the UK,Most shows Ive seen take the same commercial breaks (albeit a little skewed timing wise) as the original program did. They have to to maintain the 30 min time slot. Are some not like that? ,"[('30', 'CARDINAL')]"
65,Question about Hulu Live TV and local channels,Yes...,[]
66,Question about Hulu Live TV and local channels,Thank you! ,[]
67,AHL TV free streaming. Oct 5-8,Here is the link for more info:https://theahl.com/watch-opening-weekend-free-ahltv,[]
68,Wife wants to watch cooking channel,"Philo - $20 /month for tier that includes Cooking Channel, and you can DVR it","[('Philo', 'GPE'), ('20 /month', 'DATE'), ('DVR', 'ORG')]"
69,Wife wants to watch cooking channel,PlayStation Vue Core tier has Cooking Channel and you can DVR good eats.  (And you do not need a play station),"[('PlayStation Vue Core', 'PRODUCT'), ('DVR', 'ORG')]"
70,Wife wants to watch cooking channel,"Most cable shows are available for digital purchase on iTunes/Amazon/Google Play with episodes released the day after they are broadcast. I’m not familiar with the show. There’s are 15 seasons listed on iTunes but the newest episode appears to be from about 2011. Assuming this is some sort of revival. Check one of these outlets shortly before the premier and see if they are selling a season pass. It will probably cost under $30 for all episodes and you’ll own them to stream whenever you wish. Second best option would be Philo subscription for $20 per month. Wait until a few weeks into the season for the first few episodes to be archived on-demand, and she can probably binge the entire season for 1 or 2 months’ fees. ","[('iTunes/Amazon/Google Play', 'ORG'), ('the day', 'DATE'), ('15', 'CARDINAL'), ('iTunes', 'ORG'), ('about 2011', 'DATE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('under $30', 'MONEY'), ('Second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Philo', 'GPE'), ('20', 'MONEY'), ('a few weeks', 'DATE'), ('the season', 'DATE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('the entire season', 'DATE'), ('1', 'CARDINAL')]"
71,Wife wants to watch cooking channel,You can check and see if the season is for sale On iTunes and Amazon. ,"[('iTunes', 'ORG'), ('Amazon', 'ORG')]"
72,Looking to finally cut cord in Pittsburgh. Need advice.,That really comes down to what's avalible in your area you need to figure out who services your area so unless you want to post your exact address here at least come back with a list of service providers avalible to you.,[]
73,Looking to finally cut cord in Pittsburgh. Need advice.,We are with Xfinity at the moment. Verizon also services our area. ,"[('Verizon', 'ORG')]"
74,Looking to finally cut cord in Pittsburgh. Need advice.,"I'm from the area and I went with Hulu. We get just about everything that we got with cable. I also like Directv Now since it pretty much replaces cable with all the channels, but it can be buggy. They need to work some things out which I'm sure they will.I guess I should ask, what are you looking to watch? ","[('Hulu', 'GPE'), ('Directv', 'PERSON')]"
75,Looking to finally cut cord in Pittsburgh. Need advice.,Fios has been having a $39.99 internet only package that would be worth looking into. ,"[('39.99', 'MONEY')]"
76,Which ecosystem is best for buying TV Seasons?,"They’re all pretty synonymous when it comes to purchasing tv seasons. Amazon has the added benefit of their prime video platform, if you’re a prime member.","[('Amazon', 'ORG')]"
77,Which ecosystem is best for buying TV Seasons?,"I am.  From what I understand I could still access that through the AppleTV though, correct?  Though I thought I heard something about the Amazon AppleTV app not supporting surround sound, though that could’ve been old news and maybe it’s fixed.  ","[('Amazon', 'ORG')]"
78,Which ecosystem is best for buying TV Seasons?,"I think Amazon might be a little cheaper for some shows, if you care about pricing at that level. I recommend doing the DirectTV Now promo where you prepay a few months of the service and get a ""free"" Apple TV 4k. You can stream from Apple and Amazon's libraries with it. Extra perk (in my opinion) is you can download your purchased apple content onto your laptop for offline viewing. Amazon only allows offline viewing for tablets and phones.","[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('DirectTV', 'ORG'), ('a few months', 'DATE'), ('Apple TV', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Amazon', 'ORG')]"
79,Which ecosystem is best for buying TV Seasons?,"Darn, looks like that expired, that did look like it was a solid deal.  Being able to download to a laptop is a plus.  ",[]
80,Which ecosystem is best for buying TV Seasons?,"I prefer amazon but don’t have a really good reason why them over any other and if you’re going to try crunchyroll try vrv its crunchy+funimation+drama fever+mubi,shutter,mondo,nicksplat for 10 bucks crazy good deal ","[('10 bucks', 'MONEY')]"
81,Which ecosystem is best for buying TV Seasons?,Two things:1) I’ll echo what everyone else has said and say amazon would be my recommendation.Amazon has a tv app on pretty much all major platforms from iOS to Xbox.  So it gives you flexibility to watch your shows even if you decide to change platforms. 2) have you considered a cord cutter tv service instead of buying the shows individually?  I only ask because I use youtubetv and watch pretty much all of the same shows you do.  It’s still a fraction of the price of dish ($40 a month) and has the added bonus of not having to wait 24 hours for the episodes to come up.,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Xbox', 'ORG'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('40', 'MONEY'), ('24 hours', 'TIME')]"
82,Which ecosystem is best for buying TV Seasons?,"Going with the AppleTV and buying through Amazon seems like it may be the way to go. On YouTube TV, I haven’t paid much attention to it, are the shows in HD and with at least 5.1 Dolby Digital on it?","[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('YouTube TV', 'ORG'), ('at least 5.1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Dolby Digital', 'ORG')]"
83,Which ecosystem is best for buying TV Seasons?,"Honestly,  while I use an Apple TV as my main device I buy TV shows from Amazon, Vudu, and iTunes to get the best deals. All of those sources are viewable on my Apple TV. Granted on my Roku or Shield I can’t access the iTunes purchases but that isn’t that big of a deal to me. I really like being able to shop for the best deal on seasons or catching  seasons on sale on the different services yet still being able to access them.  Since you own an Apple TV I would say don’t just stick with the one store and instead shop around for the best prices. ","[(' ', 'NORP'), ('Apple TV', 'ORG'), ('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Vudu', 'PERSON'), ('iTunes', 'GPE'), ('Apple TV', 'ORG'), ('Roku', 'GPE'), ('Shield', 'PERSON'), ('iTunes', 'PERSON'), ('Apple TV', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
84,Which ecosystem is best for buying TV Seasons?,"Not all apps are available on every front end. It's all about content control. Amazon isn't chromecastable. It's available on android os, like the nvidia shield.If you're locked into Apple already then your options are limited.   Apple locks down their ecosystem pretty hard. If you start buying on itunes then you have to use things that work with itunes. I think the nvidia shield is the best front end. Roku also has decent app support, due to it not competing on content.","[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('Roku', 'PERSON')]"
85,Which ecosystem is best for buying TV Seasons?,"Personally, as far as purchasing content goes, I tend to prefer device-agnostic services like Vudu.  I don't like the idea of losing access to my purchases if two companies get into a pissing match (like Google and Amazon currently are).  Out of the choices you mentioned, though, Amazon is the one with the most devices under its belt.","[('Vudu', 'PERSON'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Amazon', 'ORG')]"
86,Which ecosystem is best for buying TV Seasons?,"If you’re an Apple guy and don’t expect that to change, iTunes purchases will give you the best integration. Apple TV supports every major streaming app at this point. And it’s “TV” app does an effective job of organizing your purchased content across all apple devices, alerting you when new episodes are released, etc. But TV shows purchased thru iTunes only play on Apple devices and PCs. No android. No amazon fire. No Roku. If you want to hedge against the possibility of changing platforms, buying thru someone like Amazon or Vudu is probably wise. Depending on how much you watch, you could also consider a live streaming service like YouTube TV or PS Vue. YTTV costs $40 per month, far less than your satellite bill. It has dozens of channels and a digital DVR. ","[('Apple', 'ORG'), ('iTunes', 'PERSON'), ('Apple TV', 'ORG'), ('iTunes', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Vudu', 'PERSON'), ('YouTube TV', 'ORG'), ('PS Vue', 'ORG'), ('40', 'MONEY'), ('dozens', 'CARDINAL'), ('DVR', 'ORG')]"
87,Hulu Live vs DirecTV Now? ...,"3rd baby coming after the older 2 have gone to college?? Nice. I guess you really hated being empty nesters :). Have you considered YouTube TV at all? I find it to be the best streaming service. Between Hulu Live and DirecTV Now, you’d probably be better off with DirectTV Now being an AT&T customer. You’d get some DVR functionality without having to pay more for it and $5 HBO add-on if you watch HBO at all. ","[('3rd', 'ORDINAL'), ('YouTube TV', 'ORG'), ('AT&T', 'ORG'), ('DVR', 'ORG'), ('$5 HBO', 'MONEY'), ('HBO', 'ORG')]"
88,Hulu Live vs DirecTV Now? ...,"He meant the third would be in college. lol  Direct tv now has a great mix of channels, a 20 hr dvr ( soon to be more) and a good interface.  I did not care for hulu's interface for live, but give them or all the streaming services a try and pick what suits you.  That is what is great about cord cutting. No contracts. ","[('third', 'ORDINAL'), ('20', 'CARDINAL')]"
89,TV stations still on VHF-LO band,"METV in NYC, the #1 market, has been RF 3 for years. I pick it up perfectly with a vhf lo antenna. Not sure what your post is supposed to be but vhf lo is not hard to get if you have the right antenna (big vhf lo antenna) and are in a good location. I see people here talking about how hard rf 6 is to get in philly (mind you, I don’t know the technical parameters of that station or how powerful it transmits) but then they say they have a Mohu Leaf. What do you expect?  That piece of garbage antenna can’t bend the laws of physics. ","[('NYC', 'GPE'), ('1', 'MONEY'), ('RF', 'ORG'), ('3 for years', 'DATE'), ('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mohu Leaf', 'ORG')]"
90,TV stations still on VHF-LO band,"The history of your station is fascinating: "" The station, originally located in Ely, Nevada, signed on July 9, 2001 as KVNV, a satellite of KVBC, the NBC affiliate in Las Vegas....... The owner sought permission to reallocate KVNV from Ely to  New Jersey, as part of a legal loophole that allows any VHF station that moves to a state with no FCC-licensed commercial VHF stations to receive automatic permission to move. - ""(The loophole was set up because many New Jersey TV viewers felt shortchanged that nearly all their commercial TV stations came from either New York City or Philadelphia, not from their own state.)""","[('Ely', 'GPE'), ('Nevada', 'GPE'), ('July 9, 2001', 'DATE'), ('KVNV', 'PERSON'), ('KVBC', 'GPE'), ('NBC', 'ORG'), ('Las Vegas', 'GPE'), ('KVNV', 'PERSON'), (' New Jersey', 'LOC'), ('FCC', 'ORG'), ('New Jersey TV', 'GPE'), ('New York City', 'GPE'), ('Philadelphia', 'GPE')]"
91,TV stations still on VHF-LO band,"WRGB Schenenctady is transmitting on their historical assignment of channel 6.  When the DTV transition started, they were comfortably and reliably on channel 39.  After the analog shutdown, they moved back to 6 much to everyone's dismay.  Why they didn't stay on 39, I have no clue.","[('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('39', 'CARDINAL'), ('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('39', 'DATE')]"
92,TV stations still on VHF-LO band,"Most DTV stations returned to their original channel when the 2009 shutdown happened (example: My channels 8, 10, 11, 12, 13 left UHF and returned to their old historical channels).   - As for your station, probably because 39 was allocated to someone else.  And even if they had kept 39, they would have been bumped by the FCC Auction which sold all channels above 37.","[('2009', 'DATE'), ('8', 'CARDINAL'), ('10', 'DATE'), ('11', 'DATE'), ('12', 'DATE'), ('13', 'CARDINAL'), ('39', 'CARDINAL'), ('39', 'CARDINAL'), ('the FCC Auction', 'ORG'), ('37', 'CARDINAL')]"
93,Best streaming device?,"I have tried and used them all and ended up with all Roku devices in my home because they have the most apps, are easiest to use, and basically never buffer. AndroidTV boxes like Mibox have limited app support, crash frequently, and the chromecast option has many issues. Chromecast devices require you to use your phone instead of a remote which is fine for one person but inconvenient for family. FireTV is missing some google apps like youtube and play movies and firesticks buffer way more than Roku sticks or Chromecast.  AppleTV is great if you are deep in the Apple ecosystem and need to mirror Mac and iphone screens otherwise its too expensive and the remote is terrible. ","[('Roku', 'PERSON'), ('Mibox', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Roku', 'PERSON'), ('Chromecast', 'PERSON'), (' ', 'NORP'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('Mac', 'PERSON')]"
94,Best streaming device?,The best is the Nvidia Shield but the most reliable is Roku.,"[('the Nvidia Shield', 'PRODUCT'), ('Roku', 'PERSON')]"
95,Best streaming device?,really a personal choice each has strengths and weaknesses. as a pure video streaming service device i went with rokus but i also have a 3rd gen apple tv so i am covered for any itunes purchases or rentals. the shield tv has a lot of positives but a few drawbacks as does the newer 4th gen and 4k apple tv. there’s not one size fits all.,"[('3rd', 'ORDINAL'), ('4th', 'ORDINAL'), ('4k', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
96,Best streaming device?,"I think you are overlapping two different things.  I use in combination both a Sony Android TV and a Roku box as well.I like the Sony TV for loading up my own unique Android apps, and the use of the Google Assistant.  You also forgot to mention the Bluetooth and the built-in Chromecast on Sony TVs which I find super handy as well!But for just regular video streaming apps like Netflix, Prime, Pluto, etc,, the Roku is the simplest and most convenient device to use. The Smart TVs (all brands) just are a little too clumsy to use for this purpose.  Plus the Roku has by far the most channel choices which is very beneficial also.","[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sony Android TV', 'ORG'), ('Roku', 'GPE'), ('Sony', 'ORG'), ('Android', 'PRODUCT'), ('the Google Assistant', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Bluetooth', 'GPE'), ('Chromecast', 'LOC'), ('Sony', 'ORG'), ('Netflix', 'PERSON'), ('Roku', 'PERSON'), ('Smart', 'PERSON')]"
97,Best streaming device?,"ROKU FOR LIFE.  No seriously, my Roku 3 from 5 year ago still is the most used device in my house.  Going to jump to the ultra 4k unit soon.  Supports all the major stream services I use (youtube, casting, hbo, hulu, netflix, prime video and more).  Simple interface, good load times, ease of use for everyone. ","[('ROKU FOR LIFE', 'ORG'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('5 year ago', 'DATE'), (' ', 'ORDINAL'), ('4k', 'CARDINAL')]"
98,Best streaming device?,"I love my Shield, but not having certain apps on the Android store has been a hassle. ","[('Shield', 'PERSON'), ('Android', 'ORG')]"
99,Best streaming device?,"Although I mostly use Roku, I see consistently better performance from my Amazon Fire 4k TV Box. DirecTV Now is great with the Amazon Fire but so slow as to be unusable through Roku.Still, I mostly use Roku because Philo is better through Roku and both TVs in-house are Roku TVs.","[('Roku', 'PERSON'), ('Amazon Fire', 'ORG'), ('Amazon Fire', 'FAC'), ('Roku', 'GPE'), ('Roku', 'GPE'), ('Philo', 'GPE'), ('Roku', 'GPE'), ('Roku', 'GPE')]"
100,Best streaming device?,"I like Roku. It works very well and there are no conflicts with streaming apps like Fire TV and YTTV, etc. I like the remote. I got a Fire TV Pendant that works well, but I am not real crazy about the remote for some reason, so it will be getting sent back. There is nothing really out there that competes with the Roku unless you want to spend more money. ","[('Roku', 'PERSON'), ('Fire', 'PERSON'), ('YTTV', 'ORG'), ('Roku', 'PERSON')]"
101,Best streaming device?,"Lots say Apple TV 4k is the best. I have one and it is good, but I like the built in Roku aspect of my TCL tv better. ","[('Apple', 'ORG'), ('4k', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Roku', 'GPE'), ('TCL', 'ORG')]"
102,Best streaming device?,Any particular reason or reasons why? Trying to compare things.,[]
103,Best streaming device?,"I love the Apple TV, but despise the trackpad remote. I wish Apple would come out with a new remote similar to the new Fire TV remote just announced by Amazon. ","[('Apple TV', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('Amazon', 'ORG')]"
104,fuboTV Adds NBA League Pass,Nice. Fubo has been solid for me on Apple TV 4K. ,"[('Fubo', 'ORG'), ('Apple TV', 'ORG')]"
105,fuboTV Adds NBA League Pass,I’ve only trialed it. It worked well. Just wish it had abc/Disney.,[]
106,fuboTV Adds NBA League Pass,$28/month. $12 cheaper than what YTTV is offering for it.,"[('28/month', 'MONEY'), ('12', 'MONEY'), ('YTTV', 'ORG')]"
107,fuboTV Adds NBA League Pass,"Both services are using NBA’s published pricing. For whatever reason, YouTube TV is only offering the Premium, commercial free version of League Pass which retails for $40. This is the standard version with commercials for $29 per month. Same prices as buying direct from NBA.com.","[('NBA', 'ORG'), ('YouTube TV', 'ORG'), ('Premium', 'GPE'), ('League Pass', 'GPE'), ('40', 'MONEY'), ('29', 'MONEY'), ('NBA.com', 'ORG')]"
108,What antenna should we get?,How much do you care about the ION network? I ask because it is off to the east with the rest of the signals coming from north to  northwest. If you would be willing to risk not getting ION you could probably make a single antenna work. Examples:* Winegard HD7694P* Channel Master CM-2018Two combined antenna suggestion on request...,"[('ION', 'ORG'), (' ', 'NORP'), ('ION', 'GPE'), ('CM-2018Two', 'ORG')]"
109,What antenna should we get?,My personal favorite is the  [Xtreme Signal HDB8X-NI 8-Bay VHF/UHF HDTV Bowtie Antenna](https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00CXQO00K/ref=oh_aui_detailpage_o08_s00?ie=UTF8&psc=1)I tried several indoor antennas and a couple of outdoor antenna's. I found the most success and channels with this one. For me I needed a bi-directional antenna.,"[(' ', 'NORP'), ('Xtreme Signal', 'ORG'), ('Bowtie Antenna](https://www.amazon.com', 'ORG')]"
110,Locast free TV streaming service launches iOS app; tvOS version by years end,"One senses that the day when TV broadcasters freely stream their broadcasts over the internet fast approaches, just as many radio broadcasters have already done.","[('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('the day', 'DATE')]"
111,Locast free TV streaming service launches iOS app; tvOS version by years end,A handful do like Comet TV.,"[('Comet TV', 'ORG')]"
112,Locast free TV streaming service launches iOS app; tvOS version by years end,"Do any of the OTA DVRs function as FM tuners? I think that would be a really neat feature, considering the VHF antenna should pick up FM signals. I don’t mind going to a radio stations web site for streaming, but having all my local stations together and available from any device connected to my network would be something that I would use. ",[]
113,Locast free TV streaming service launches iOS app; tvOS version by years end,Nice,[]
114,Locast free TV streaming service launches iOS app; tvOS version by years end,Been using it on my Rokus that last week or so. Really great service for someone like me who has abysmal antenna reception.,"[('Rokus', 'ORG'), ('last week', 'DATE')]"
115,Locast free TV streaming service launches iOS app; tvOS version by years end,"Yeah, I have it on Roku but it isn't available in Los Angeles yet? ","[('Roku', 'PERSON'), ('Los Angeles', 'GPE')]"
116,Locast free TV streaming service launches iOS app; tvOS version by years end,Wasn't there a service that tried this already and was shutdown for copyright violations?,[]
117,Locast free TV streaming service launches iOS app; tvOS version by years end,"Aereo tried to argue that each subscriber renting a physical antenna in their warehouse meant that they could charge to be the middleman between the customer's antenna and the customer's devices via the internet. That didn't hold up in court and they were told they needed to sign rebroadcast agreements with the channels that they retransmit over the internet, which bankrupted them.Locast is different because they're a non-profit. They're operating under a clause in the FCC laws that allows non-profits to retransmit OTA broadcasts within the designated market area without getting permission from the broadcasters. I believe the clause was originally meant for rural areas where the TV signal doesn't cover the edges of the market very well, so they allow organizations setup re-transmitters to extend the range of the broadcasts, and as long as they're only transmitting within the designated market area, and not making money off the broadcasts, and they don't need the channels' permission.Locast is arguing that clause applies to internet broadcasts as well since it can be difficult to receive OTA broadcasts in cities due to interference and tall buildings and such, so as long as they're only broadcasting within the designated market area (they make you create an account and verify your location), they feel that retransmitting over the internet without the channel's permission is legal (Unlike Aereo which was a for profit business). I'm sure they'll be challenged on this in court sooner or later and we'll see if that defense holds up.","[('Aereo', 'GPE'), ('FCC', 'ORG'), ('Locast', 'PERSON'), ('OTA', 'ORG'), ('Aereo', 'GPE')]"
118,Locast free TV streaming service launches iOS app; tvOS version by years end,Aereo,"[('Aereo', 'GPE')]"
119,Locast free TV streaming service launches iOS app; tvOS version by years end,Thanks did not know that this even existed. Any way to DVR from it? ,"[('DVR', 'ORG')]"
120,Locast free TV streaming service launches iOS app; tvOS version by years end,No,[]
121,Locast free TV streaming service launches iOS app; tvOS version by years end,[removed],[]
122,Locast free TV streaming service launches iOS app; tvOS version by years end,Awesome!!,[]
123,Locast free TV streaming service launches iOS app; tvOS version by years end,"Holy crap. I had no idea this existed.I don't care about the Apple stuff, but there is already android app. One way or another that gets it on my Shield.I live about 60 miles away from the tv station attennaes with challenging terrain. I would need a big honking roof antennae to even have a chance. Because of this, I've still been paying Dish for locals.This is really big for me and I'll be loading it tomorrow and evaluating for awhile. This is excellent. Thank you. ","[('Apple', 'ORG'), ('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('Shield', 'PERSON'), ('about 60 miles', 'QUANTITY'), ('Dish', 'LANGUAGE')]"
124,Locast free TV streaming service launches iOS app; tvOS version by years end,Has anyone with a developer iOS device tried changing their location with this app to see if they can ‘trick’ the app and receive different cities? ,[]
125,How Cable Has Fueled OTT,"strikes me that Cable fueled OTT by driving the costs of a package up.Cable should cost significantly less then the electric bill, instead it's significantly more.","[('Cable', 'ORG')]"
126,How Cable Has Fueled OTT,"Agree 100%.  Cable will blame it on rising entertainment costs, but somehow OTT has managed to keep costs down.  Gee, maybe it's because they don't gouge their customers?  In my area cable has now taken to jacking up ISP prices continually, probably because they are bleeding TV subs.  I'm just lucky I have an alternative, most people don't (yet).  But when they do, cable will be headed out the door, as they should be, the greedy suckers!","[('Agree 100%', 'ORG'), ('Cable', 'ORG'), ('OTT', 'ORG'), ('ISP', 'FAC')]"
127,How Cable Has Fueled OTT,"> As the demand for bandwidth kept increasing, service providers obliged........  When bandwidth is 1 Gbit/s, there is no congestion and thus no need to prioritize. Without congestion, an OTT edge service provider can get its traffic through as well as virtually any in-house prioritized service.> Not only are OTT voice players able to compete, but OTT video players can thrive. ","[('OTT', 'ORG')]"
128,Over-The-Top Video Apps Experience a 67 Percent Drop in Subscribers Within the First Two Months,"Yeah, that's usually when the free trials end. ",[]
129,Over-The-Top Video Apps Experience a 67 Percent Drop in Subscribers Within the First Two Months,">To increase engagement on an app, a company suggests using in-app notifications or emails to suggest relevant content based on the user’s first in-app conversion event. For example, if a user prefers horror movies, it should push them to watch “suggested content” in the same or related genres. It also suggests running personalized push notifications or email campaigns to inform repeat users of new content.”>Sure-fire ways to get me to cancel.Also: any company who speaks of “conversion event”",[]
130,Over-The-Top Video Apps Experience a 67 Percent Drop in Subscribers Within the First Two Months,"Funny, right? I hate this as well and I just shake my head when I hear people complain, for example, about the Roku interface because I immediately hated the Apple TV and Fire Stick upon using them because of all the ""suggested"" content aggregated on the homepage. Just give me a list of my channels/apps and let me do the work. I don't need notifications, emails or content suggestions pulled together from 17 different apps into one place.","[('Apple TV', 'ORG'), ('Stick', 'FAC'), ('17', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
131,Over-The-Top Video Apps Experience a 67 Percent Drop in Subscribers Within the First Two Months,"Amen, man. If your product is shit, I’m not sticking around for you to bombard me with bonus shit",[]
132,Tried YTTV and live sports were sped up at times and it lagged a lot in between.,It’s probably the chrome cast.We use YouTube TV on four different Apple TVs in our house and I’ve never encountered that at all… And all we do is watch sports for the most part,"[('YouTube TV', 'ORG'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
133,Tried YTTV and live sports were sped up at times and it lagged a lot in between.,"Ty all for the replies.  Based on popular opinion, it seems as if it's the Chromecast",[]
134,Tried YTTV and live sports were sped up at times and it lagged a lot in between.,"YTTV on gen 1 chromecast is known to be a poor experience. They even put a warning banner on the loading screen that says you may have trouble. I've used YTTV on Android TV, multiple Rokus, PC and mobile and every other platform is way better than gen 1 chromecast in terms of video quality/performance.","[('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Android TV', 'ORG'), ('Rokus', 'PERSON'), ('1', 'CARDINAL')]"
135,Tried YTTV and live sports were sped up at times and it lagged a lot in between.,https://www.reddit.com/r/youtubetv/comments/9l1dkd/will_upgrading_my_1st_gen_chromecast_help_with/OP deleted their post for some reason. But they were complaining of the same thing while watching sports.,[]
136,Tried YTTV and live sports were sped up at times and it lagged a lot in between.,"I’d echo others here. I use YTTV with a Roku ultra, and I’ve yet to have any issues.",[]
137,Tried YTTV and live sports were sped up at times and it lagged a lot in between.,"For the 3 months I had YTTV it was great. I just didn't use it enough to justify the cost. I used it nearly exclusively on a Chromecast as well. It's a second gen I believe, had my first gen bent at my parents house.","[('the 3 months', 'DATE'), ('Chromecast', 'ORG'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
138,Looking for an advice.,Vue. For sure.  You can watch on tablets or laptop.   You could get a cheap hd tv and roku or fire stick and enjoy,[]
139,Looking for an advice.,Sling,"[('Sling', 'ORG')]"
140,Looking for an advice.,"Streaming services need to independently contract with local affiliates to carry the major broadcast networks. That includes your local stations for ABC, NBC, CBS, Fox and (to a lesser degree) CW. Plug your zip code in the website of several services and see if live ABC (and others) is offered. You may also want to look at Regional Sports Networks as those will carry dozens of games for your local teams. If you’re an NBA fan, give some consideration to NBA TV. YouTube Tv has NBA channel in its plan for $40. PS Vue has it in their $50 plan. Hulu doesn’t carry that network. Directv Now is another option but do yourself a favor and consider it a last resort. It’s been around for nearly 2 years now and is still maddeningly unreliable. ","[('ABC', 'ORG'), ('NBC', 'ORG'), ('CBS', 'ORG'), ('Fox', 'ORG'), ('ABC', 'ORG'), ('Regional Sports Networks', 'ORG'), ('dozens', 'CARDINAL'), ('NBA', 'ORG'), ('NBA TV', 'ORG'), ('YouTube Tv', 'ORG'), ('NBA', 'ORG'), ('40', 'MONEY'), ('PS Vue', 'ORG'), ('50', 'MONEY'), ('Hulu', 'GPE'), ('Directv Now', 'PERSON'), ('nearly 2 years', 'DATE')]"
141,Looking for an advice.,"Thanks for the detailed advice. Feels like my best bet is either Youtube channel or Hulu. They are $10 cheaper than Vue, and has all local sport channel, tnt, espn and abc. Youtube has NBA channel, so that would be a plus, but are they pretty much the same in terms of quality?","[('Youtube', 'ORG'), ('Hulu', 'GPE'), ('10', 'MONEY'), ('Youtube', 'ORG'), ('NBA', 'ORG')]"
142,Looking for an advice.,Why not just get the nba package?,[]
143,"T-Mobile is currently selling TV services, and here’s what it looks like",$90 a month. $110 a month if you're not a T-Mobile subscriber.And no local or premium channels.That's what it looks like.,"[('90', 'MONEY'), ('110', 'MONEY')]"
144,"T-Mobile is currently selling TV services, and here’s what it looks like","They have local channels according to that brochure, at that location. ",[]
145,"T-Mobile is currently selling TV services, and here’s what it looks like","Super disappointing price point from T-mobile. I think I’ll stick with YouTube TV for less than half that, thanks.I’m not sure what exact market they’re targeting here, because it’s certainly not the live-streaming one.","[('YouTube TV', 'ORG'), ('less than half', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
146,"T-Mobile is currently selling TV services, and here’s what it looks like",hahahahahaha! Good luck with that. ,[]
147,"T-Mobile is currently selling TV services, and here’s what it looks like",That is really expensive. I get most of the channels if not all listed in the brochure for about $50 using a streaming service.,"[('about $50', 'MONEY')]"
148,"T-Mobile is currently selling TV services, and here’s what it looks like","I think our FIOS internet+TV would be be a little more than $100 where we are. IDK - don't need TV that bad, however having a lot of documentary channels would be nice.","[('a little more than $100', 'MONEY')]"
149,"T-Mobile is currently selling TV services, and here’s what it looks like",Should this even be posted here since it's not cutting the cord?  It's hooking the cord back up.,[]
150,"T-Mobile is currently selling TV services, and here’s what it looks like",Be Warned. The cord you need to cut may be wireless. ,[]
151,"T-Mobile is currently selling TV services, and here’s what it looks like",I have a feeling whatever they come up with next is not going to reflect what the current Layer3 offering is.  I have seen a couple other articles which say T-Mobile is experimenting with other packages.  We shall see.,"[('Layer3', 'ORG'), ('Mobile', 'GPE')]"
152,"T-Mobile is currently selling TV services, and here’s what it looks like","It’s still a cable box at the end of they day. Unless they get it down to YTTV type pricing, and include locals, they are dead in the water. ","[('the end of they day', 'DATE')]"
153,"T-Mobile is currently selling TV services, and here’s what it looks like",Ya this has to be a starting point to offer smaller internet only packages.  T-Mobile has been pretty smart with some of this stuff so this can't be the end game.,"[('Mobile', 'GPE')]"
154,"T-Mobile is currently selling TV services, and here’s what it looks like",This is basically just the existing Layer3 TV being sold through T-Mobile now. Doubt this is what T-Mobile has been working on after purchasing Layer3.,"[('Layer3 TV', 'ORG'), ('Layer3', 'ORG')]"
155,"T-Mobile is currently selling TV services, and here’s what it looks like","Alright! T-mobile, the uncarrier, will understand what ""disruption"" *is* for the TV industry, right?>service starts at $90/month... Welp. ","[('90/month', 'MONEY'), ('Welp', 'GPE')]"
156,"T-Mobile is currently selling TV services, and here’s what it looks like","Exactly. This isn't disruptive in the sense their other uncarrier initiatives have been. It is the opposite. Cable TV, only less convenient and harder to navigate. Ugh!","[('Cable TV', 'ORG')]"
157,"T-Mobile is currently selling TV services, and here’s what it looks like",Maybe it's $90 a month including delivery so you don't have to worry about data caps.,"[('90', 'MONEY')]"
158,"T-Mobile is currently selling TV services, and here’s what it looks like","if it included home 5G service, this would actually be a great deal.  I would consider switching over from my $60 a month 500/50 internet plan and $40 a month YouTube TV I have now.  ","[('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('60', 'MONEY'), ('500/50', 'NORP'), ('40', 'MONEY'), ('YouTube TV', 'ORG')]"
159,"T-Mobile is currently selling TV services, and here’s what it looks like",I just got a notice yesterday that their tv app has been phased out,"[('yesterday', 'DATE')]"
160,Advice on Antenna to Also Receive ABC (TVFool Link Inside),"Check this out:* https://rabbitears.info/market.php?request=station_search&callsign=week#stationWEEK is transmitting NBC/ABC/CW, all in HD. Probably not great for  bit rate but if you are happy with that source of ABC, then everything gets a lot easier. Everything in the UHF band and close. So an indoor antenna is definitely worth trying. For the attic a 4 bay UHF antenna would be more than good. Examples:* Digiwave ANT2084, ANT2085* Stellar Labs 30-2426* Solid Signal XS HDB4X AKA Digiwave ANT2086* Channel Master CM4221HD* Antennas Direct DB4e","[('NBC', 'ORG'), ('ABC/CW', 'ORG'), ('ABC', 'ORG'), ('UHF', 'ORG'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('UHF', 'ORG'), ('ANT2085', 'GPE'), ('Stellar', 'GPE'), ('30-2426', 'DATE'), ('Solid Signal XS', 'ORG'), ('Channel Master CM4221HD', 'ORG'), ('Antennas Direct', 'ORG')]"
161,Advice on Antenna to Also Receive ABC (TVFool Link Inside),"Thanks for the information!  I hadn't noticed that ABC was also on that band.  Only at 720p, but that's the best I can seem to get for most of the stations in central IL.https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B008KVUAGU - I picked up this Mediasonic Homeworx antenna about 3 years ago as a quick test to see what would be possible, but now I'm looking to get more serious about cutting out Comcast and switching fully to a fiber internet solution with an antenna (and probably a Tablo once I figure out the antenna situation.)I guess I could pick up something a bit more expensive and see how the stations come in.  Right now reception isn't that great, but I'm attributing that to the antenna being on the west side of the house and maybe 2ft above floor level due to mounting issues.EDIT:  I was planning on getting the antenna ""just right"" then focusing on picking up a 4-channel Tablo around Black Friday.  I have a closet with an east-facing window that I could plug in the Tablo and the antenna.  It'd all be out of the way and a LOT simpler than trying to route coax from the attic to the basement (where most of my network infrastructure is).  I'm liking the indoor antenna option a lot more now!","[('ABC', 'ORG'), ('720p', 'CARDINAL'), ('IL.https://www.amazon.com', 'ORG'), ('Mediasonic Homeworx', 'ORG'), ('about 3 years ago', 'DATE'), ('Comcast', 'ORG'), ('Tablo', 'ORG'), ('situation.)I', 'GPE'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('4-channel', 'CARDINAL'), ('Black Friday', 'EVENT'), ('Tablo', 'PERSON'), ('LOT', 'ORG')]"
162,Advice on Antenna to Also Receive ABC (TVFool Link Inside),"You want to use this, not TV Fool at the moment.https://www.fcc.gov/media/engineering/dtvmaps",[]
163,Advice on Antenna to Also Receive ABC (TVFool Link Inside),"Thanks for the link!  I've gone through a few different links to see if I can get a quorum on what I can reasonably expect.  With the relatively low quality of the antenna I have right now I'm not 100% confident if certain stations are just difficult for me to receive (coming in blocky), or if the poor quality of the antenna is skewing my perception.","[('100%', 'PERCENT')]"
164,Finally took the cord cutting leap last month. I need suggestions.,"If you have certain AT&T unlimited wireless plans, you can get the normally $15/mo. Watch TV service for free and it has AMC. Philo also has AMC for $16 but has the added benefit of a cloud dvr and somewhat (imo) better on demand, since you can log into the various websites or tv anywhere apps. (Just in case you aren't home when TWD airs. It happens...)","[('AT&T', 'ORG'), ('15/mo', 'MONEY'), ('AMC', 'ORG'), ('Philo', 'PERSON'), ('AMC', 'ORG'), ('16', 'MONEY'), ('TWD', 'ORG')]"
165,Finally took the cord cutting leap last month. I need suggestions.,"I'm doing a trial with Sling Blue now. It's only $25 per month and you can screen three devices at the same time, so sharing a plan with family or friends is possible. It has AMC, including some old TWD shows on demand ","[('Sling Blue', 'ORG'), ('only $25', 'MONEY'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('AMC', 'ORG'), ('TWD', 'ORG')]"
166,Finally took the cord cutting leap last month. I need suggestions.,https://redd.it/9bq6ku,[]
167,Vidgo Nears Debut of National OTT-TV Service,"This service was teased a few years ago at CES. It looks like they decided to focus or add the Latino market. There will be several Latino focused packages. That means it will go up against Sling TV International, Fubo TV and possibly DirecTV Now which recently started introducing packages in other languages besides English. I  can't tell if they will have many English language channels  or a separate plan.","[('a few years ago', 'DATE'), ('CES', 'ORG'), ('Latino', 'PERSON'), ('Latino', 'PERSON'), ('Sling TV International', 'ORG'), ('Fubo TV', 'ORG'), ('Now', 'DATE'), ('English', 'LANGUAGE'), ('English', 'LANGUAGE'), (' ', 'NORP')]"
168,Vidgo Nears Debut of National OTT-TV Service,Talk about late to the party. I wonder how well they'll be able to do this late in the game. At least they're launching out of the gate with broad platform support.,[]
169,Vidgo Nears Debut of National OTT-TV Service,"I suspect that was one of the reasons for the pivot to Latino channels. Plus they may be been cheaper to acquire rights for.  They really should consider getting rights to Japanse channels for another package as that is probably the most unserved markets here. Otherwise, it will be impossible for them to make much headway.","[('Latino', 'PERSON'), ('Japanse', 'PERSON')]"
170,YouTube TV rolling out full DVR control on more channels,I seriously want to get YouTube TV but doesn’t have Viacom stuff. Getting so sick of Direct TV now ,"[('YouTube TV', 'ORG'), ('Viacom', 'ORG'), ('Direct TV', 'ORG')]"
171,YouTube TV rolling out full DVR control on more channels,Add Philo,"[('Add Philo', 'PERSON')]"
172,Save $20 On a New 4K Fire Stick By Trading In Your Old Streaming Box (Even If It’s Busted).,"So, even the 2nd gen Roku from 9 years ago that I have laying around would count? XD","[('2nd', 'DATE'), ('Roku', 'PERSON'), ('9 years ago', 'DATE'), ('XD', 'GPE')]"
173,Save $20 On a New 4K Fire Stick By Trading In Your Old Streaming Box (Even If It’s Busted).,"Thanks for sharing this! Doesn't work for amazon devices ie an old stick, but I have an old Chromecast that's getting the boot. ","[('Chromecast', 'PERSON')]"
174,Save $20 On a New 4K Fire Stick By Trading In Your Old Streaming Box (Even If It’s Busted).,Does this apply in Canada?,"[('Canada', 'GPE')]"
175,Save $20 On a New 4K Fire Stick By Trading In Your Old Streaming Box (Even If It’s Busted).,Thanks for the heads up! Sending them a Roku LT that I had no use for.,"[('Roku LT', 'ORG')]"
176,Save $20 On a New 4K Fire Stick By Trading In Your Old Streaming Box (Even If It’s Busted).,May have to send in my launch day chromecast. ,"[('May', 'DATE')]"
177,HD Homerun question,It should work fine on a local network with no Internet.  I suspect what happened is that your app on the Mac didn't know enough to check for a local address and instead was attempting to use the regular router DNS.   Did you try to connect using the actual IP of the HD Homerun?,"[('Mac', 'PERSON'), ('DNS', 'ORG'), ('the HD Homerun', 'ORG')]"
178,HD Homerun question,I could get to it in chrome but the mac app wouldn't connect to it.,[]
179,HD Homerun question,>...I could connect to it over my wifi...You mean through a WiFi router connected to the HDHR with a cable? That should work. What does the diagnostic app/program show you?,"[('WiFi', 'ORG'), ('HDHR', 'ORG')]"
180,HD Homerun question,"I couldn't use the app on my imac.  You would of thought it would work, just with no channel guide.",[]
181,HD Homerun question,Should work (but we only use wired LAN connections).,"[('LAN', 'ORG')]"
182,HD Homerun question,"DHCP needs to be working somewhere in this scenario, either on the router or on you Macbook.   If you temporarily setup a DHCP server on your macbook and connect the HDHR with ethernet directly you should have success.","[('  ', 'ORG'), ('HDHR', 'ORG')]"
183,HD Homerun question,DHCP was working.  The macbook was connected to wireless but the app on my macbook wouldn't open for it.,[]
184,"Poor reception with first antenna, what next?","> Ideally, I'd like to receive all of the locals down to FOX. Fox is going to require an outdoor antenna.  And you have an additional issue in that your stations are ~180º apart.   I generally don't recommend this antenna, but a DB8E might work for you.  Point it at the Fox station, and it's back lobes will pick up the other stations. The Solid Signal 8 bay bow tie should work good too.  ","[('FOX', 'ORG'), ('Fox', 'ORG'), ('~180º', 'ORG'), (' ', 'ORDINAL'), ('Point', 'ORG'), ('Fox', 'ORG'), ('The Solid Signal 8', 'ORG')]"
185,"Poor reception with first antenna, what next?","Thanks, DB8E ordered. We'll see how it does!",[]
186,"Poor reception with first antenna, what next?",">I'd be okay with an attic mount too, assuming it solved the problems. Would it be that much better for me than a living room antenna?Yes. Don't expect to get Fox without an attic antenna.","[('Fox', 'ORG')]"
187,"Poor reception with first antenna, what next?","I'm no expert, but I'll share my experience as a relatively new cordcutter. I got a cheap amplified indoor antenna and picked up only a handful of channels.  Then I replaced my old satellite dish with an RCA Yagi outdoor/attic antenna and pick up over 120 channels.  Most of my towers are in the same general direction from my house, though.Personally, I wouldn't bother with another flat/indoor antenna in your situation.  Maybe consider a bowtie or other multidirectional antenna?  Could always get one from Walmart and return it if it doesn't work well.  ","[('120', 'QUANTITY'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Walmart', 'GPE')]"
188,"Poor reception with first antenna, what next?",If you want to go with an attic antenna and have a BJ's near you they have a Clearstream 4 for $79 right now.  This goes for $100 to $149.00  everywhere else.  It does UHF and VHF.  I have not tried this model so I can't comment on the performance.,"[('BJ', 'GPE'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('79', 'MONEY'), ('100', 'MONEY'), ('149.00', 'MONEY')]"
189,"Poor reception with first antenna, what next?",>The 1byone box says it gets 28dB gain  ...That type of antenna would have negative gain. They are trying to confuse you by quoting the amplifier gain. Two entirely different things.Make sure the antenna is kept away from things that can cause interference like electronics and LED/CFL lights. Try turning stuff off to check.,"[('1byone', 'CARDINAL'), ('28dB', 'CARDINAL'), ('Two', 'CARDINAL')]"
190,"Poor reception with first antenna, what next?","I started with a Mohu Leaf, very unsatisfactory. Got a ClearStream 2, much much better. Bearing in mind that the ClearStream used indoors needs some space in front of a window, it sits on a table.","[('Mohu Leaf', 'ORG'), ('ClearStream', 'ORG')]"
191,"Poor reception with first antenna, what next?","> The 1byone box says it gets 28dB gain28 Gain is for the amplifier, and it's probably just amplifying Noise because the antenna is too small to capture the signal.   Unfortunately your stations are in multiple directions.  I think I'd try a CM4228 in your living room (no amplifier), aimed towards 254 degrees (west) and get the other stations off the backside of the CM4228. - If that works, then move it to the attic.Another option is this Flatwave Air (the black colored one): http://www.winegard.com/flatwave  Or this hyperstrong antenna: http://dennysantennaservice.com/hd_stacker_tv_antenna-html.html","[('1byone', 'CARDINAL'), ('28dB', 'CARDINAL'), ('CM4228', 'CARDINAL'), ('254 degrees', 'QUANTITY'), ('CM4228', 'CARDINAL'), ('this Flatwave Air', 'ORG'), (' ', 'NORP')]"
192,"Poor reception with first antenna, what next?",are these any good?                               https://www.walmart.com/ip/ONN-4K-HD-Motorized-Outdoor-TV-Antenna-with-150-Mile-Range-and-Pole-Mounting-Kit/56136522?u1=fe2.4.2Ahk.0.1G70P6.1iEpBA.P8.P7.3&oid=223073.1&wmlspartner=isIkAyUyNbM&sourceid=35492000643295469751&affillinktype=10&veh=aff,[]
193,"Poor reception with first antenna, what next?","CM4228, an old design, placed in an attic is not going to work for this guy.  Stay away from the Flatwave Air.  That stacked antenna must be outside, and it will not be good for his situation either.  Its beam is too tight.","[('CM4228', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Flatwave Air', 'ORG')]"
194,"Poor reception with first antenna, what next?","You'll probably want an omnidirectional antenna of some kind, because your best channels are coming in from multiple directions.Fox will be troublesome though because it's 2Edge, which means it has to bend over high terrain to get to you. You might be able to get it with an omnidirectional, but it'll be finicky. Tilting the antenna up in the direction of the Fox channel could help, but it might degrade the reception of the channels coming in the opposite direction.","[('Fox', 'ORG'), ('Fox', 'ORG')]"
195,Does this antenna get VHF signals?,>It is designed to receive tv UHF/VHF signals within that range and also works for tuning in FM radio. ,"[('\xa0', 'ORG')]"
196,Does this antenna get VHF signals?,"All you did was quote the website, which I believe is lying to us.  (After all they claim ""150 mile range"" which is ridiculous.)  I'm looking for an UNbiased source, not the manufacturer's biased sales BS.","[('150 mile', 'QUANTITY'), ('BS', 'ORG')]"
197,Does this antenna get VHF signals?,"You can get acceptable high VHF reception with a 22"" or thereabouts long dipole antenna. I was getting pretty good reception with a VHF add on kit to a clear stream antenna at 63 miles from the towers. I think that last element is a folded dipole so it may get reasonable reception.I saw a review of this kind of antenna along with Winegard, Channel Master, and a ""stacker"" design at  http://dennysantennaservice.com/best-tv-antenna.htmlIt came in last, but the other info there may help you decide on some alternatives that don't lie about their capabilities.","[('22', 'CARDINAL'), ('63 miles', 'QUANTITY'), ('Winegard', 'PERSON')]"
198,Does this antenna get VHF signals?,"The VHF-HI band used in Canada and the US is centred on 192 MHz, which has a wavelength of 299,792,458 m/s divided by 192 MHz = 1.56 metres or less than five feet.  A dipole antenna for this band, at full extension, would be half that length, about 78 cm long.","[('Canada', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('192', 'CARDINAL'), ('299,792,458 m/s', 'QUANTITY'), ('192', 'CARDINAL'), ('1.56 metres', 'QUANTITY'), ('less than five feet', 'QUANTITY'), ('half', 'CARDINAL'), ('78 cm long', 'QUANTITY')]"
199,Does this antenna get VHF signals?,> I saw a review of this kind of antenna........  http://dennysantennaservice.com/best-tv-antenna.htmlBest answer in the thread.,[]
200,Does this antenna get VHF signals?,"From retail experience and customers bringing in this antenna from amazon..... this thing is junk. My area is all Uhf so I cant answer whether it can receive vhf or not, just can tell you not to buy it. ",[]
201,Does this antenna get VHF signals?,"Kinda, probably. It has single element for the VHF-high band at the back. Yeah, it probably isn't very good for the VHF-low band but if the transmitters are close enough it might work.No one should buy a ""150 mile"" antenna for performance on any band. You buy it because you think it looks cool, is cheap and you don't care if it breaks in a few months.","[('Kinda', 'ORG'), ('150 mile', 'QUANTITY'), ('a few months', 'DATE')]"
202,Does this antenna get VHF signals?,"> VHF waves are 18 feet long, and the antenna needs to be large tooNot for VHF-Hi used for TV.   14-20 inch dipoles are what we are talking about  With that said, this is a garbage antenna.  It should be avoided.","[('18 feet', 'QUANTITY'), ('14-20 inch dipoles', 'QUANTITY'), (' ', 'NORP')]"
203,Does this antenna get VHF signals?,">>> VHF waves are 18 feet long>> Not for VHF-Hi used for TV.You seem to imply that VHF-LO is no longer used for TV (not true).   ""18 feet"" is actually the worst case (channel 2), which I probably should have taken the average instead.  If we limit ourselves to VHF-HI, we're still looking at almost 6 feet wavelength (channel 7) so you need a large antenna if the channel is used in your area.  - BTW my city uses VHF-LO (channel 6) with a wavelength over 11 feet.  I had to buy a special extra-large antenna just for that one channel.","[('18 feet', 'QUANTITY'), ('18 feet', 'QUANTITY'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('VHF-HI', 'ORG'), ('almost 6 feet', 'QUANTITY'), ('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('over 11 feet', 'QUANTITY'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
204,Senior Citizens Beginning to Rely on Cord Cutting,Please note that nocable.org sells antennas and links to it are in this article. There may also be other affiliate links contained in the article.,"[('nocable.org', 'ORG')]"
205,Senior Citizens Beginning to Rely on Cord Cutting,"I've set two people in their 80's with over-the-air antennas, and the found that is all they wanted.This is a generation that (in the USA) lived most of their life with 3 TV channels. ","[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('USA', 'GPE'), ('3', 'CARDINAL')]"
206,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series","I'm definitely excited about a potential longer form TV series, rather than films. I think a TV series would give the opportunity to better explore the other storys in the chronicles (I've always wanted to see The Magician's Nephew on screen). Having being brought up watching the 90's BBC TV series' of some of the chronicles, I think the extra breathing room given to a TV series allows a lot more development of the characters and the world that Narnia would benefit greatly from. I prefer the old TV series to the new films because of this (although probably also a heavy dose of nostalgia, i admit). &#x200B;","[('Magician', 'GPE'), ('Nephew', 'PERSON'), ('90', 'CARDINAL'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Narnia', 'GPE'), ('x200B', 'MONEY')]"
207,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series",The TV series / miniseries has been the perfect answer to movies that omit too much or film series that get dragged out past their prime.,[]
208,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series",I loved the BBC productions too.,"[('BBC', 'ORG')]"
209,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series","I'll just read the books.  I'm tired of various books getting adapted to movies and either (a) sucking or (b) not getting finished.  Narnia was supposed to be a 7-film series, but the 4th one has been stuck ""in development"" for several years.  I give up.","[('Narnia', 'PERSON'), ('7-film', 'CARDINAL'), ('4th', 'ORDINAL'), ('several years', 'DATE'), (' ', 'ORG')]"
210,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series",Those books blew my mind as a little kid.   They were my first experience reading fantasy and **POW** took me to another dimension.   ,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
211,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series",What's POW?,[]
212,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series",Very nice. With any luck they will be better than the trilogy put out by Walden Media and Disney (which was pretty good).,"[('Walden Media', 'ORG'), ('Disney', 'ORG')]"
213,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series",Disney was supposed to do all 7 books (and is currently working on movie 4)....... but per usual they did not finish what they started  :-(   The fact Harry Potter managed to get all 7 books into movies is a miracle.,"[('Disney', 'ORG'), ('7', 'CARDINAL'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), (' ', 'NORP'), ('Harry Potter', 'PERSON'), ('7', 'CARDINAL')]"
214,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series",They should just cast Tom Baker as Puddleglum again,"[('Tom Baker', 'PERSON'), ('Puddleglum', 'PERSON')]"
215,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series",>Tom Baker&#x200B;Who?  &#x200B;^(heh)&#x200B;,"[('Tom', 'PERSON'), (' &', 'ORG')]"
216,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series",[removed],[]
217,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series",What?,[]
218,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series",Just finished Prince Caspian with my 5 year old. Can't wait to see her excitement when she sees it come alive on screen!,"[('5 year old', 'DATE')]"
219,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series","Definitely sounds promising. I grew up on the audio dramas, so seeing a long-form visual media adaptation would be great. Though I'm a bit confused by what they mean by developing both films and series. Will some novels get a shorter movie, while others will get a full-length series? Or are there other spinoffs I'm not aware of that they're adapting?",[]
220,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series","I would love to see ""The Horse and His Boy"". My favorite book from the series. Hopefully they do a good job. The books are really underrated imo","[('The Horse and His Boy', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
221,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series",THIS IS TOO MUCH CONTENT!! I cant keep up :(,[]
222,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series","We most decidedly are in the golden age (of content). However from what I gather producers don’t necessarily like this as they prefer to put their eggs into one bucket. Shoot, Wasn’t that long ago there were house parties to watch Survivor. Might as well have been the 1950s! As for myself there’s no race.  I watch what I like, and there’s tons of stuff for me. I don’t watch  almost any of the Netflix junk of the week anymore. Mostly period pieces at my own pace. ","[('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Survivor', 'PERSON'), (' ', 'NORP'), ('Netflix', 'PERSON')]"
223,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series","Sounds promising, but the movies were only so-so, and I thought they were fairly true to the material. Perhaps it doesn't translate that well? Or maybe the long-form of TV will help with the pacing?",[]
224,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series","LWW, kinda true to the original, but missing a lot of things.  Prince Caspian was better, pretty true to the original book and I liked what they added.Voyage of the Dawn Treader turned into a lame video game collection plot with none of the excellent writing of C.S. Lewis and no themes of love or Christian values.  Frankly, it flat out sucked.Hopefully this will be better, but somehow I doubt it.","[('LWW', 'ORG'), ('Prince Caspian', 'PERSON'), ('C.S. Lewis', 'ORG'), ('Christian', 'NORP')]"
225,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series","Please Percy Jackson next, but I think FOX has the rights.","[('Percy Jackson', 'PERSON'), ('FOX', 'ORG')]"
226,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series",I want Ergaon as a series :(,"[('Ergaon', 'ORG')]"
227,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series",YES!!!,[]
228,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series","Books should be tv series, novellas and short stories can be movies. Really excited for a full series ",[]
229,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series","I really liked the movies they made. Liam neeson as aslan, hell yeah!","[('Liam', 'PERSON')]"
230,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series",I think you could do two episodes per book kind of like A Series of Unfortunate Events for a total of 14 episodes.,"[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('14', 'CARDINAL')]"
231,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series","Oooh Wheel of Time, Gunslinger, LotR, and Narnia? Dam netflix and Amazon gonna take over the world with Disney.&#x200B;","[('Oooh Wheel', 'PERSON'), ('Time', 'ORG'), ('Gunslinger', 'PRODUCT'), ('LotR', 'ORG'), ('Narnia', 'GPE'), ('Amazon', 'ORG')]"
232,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series","I just finished my nightly reading of the Horse and his Boy to my five yr old. In church last Sunday the speaker put up a slide of a lion and my two year old starts yelling ""Narnia! Narnia!"" At the top of his lungs.I think it's safe to say we'll be watching.","[('nightly', 'DATE'), ('Horse', 'PERSON'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('last Sunday', 'DATE'), ('two year old', 'DATE'), ('Narnia', 'GPE')]"
233,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series",There are *other* good books to use as source material Netflix. No need to just re-make every book into a TV series that has been done as a movie over the last decade.,"[('Netflix', 'PERSON'), ('the last decade', 'DATE')]"
234,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series","Well, at least with Narnia the entire franchise hasn't been adapted to the visual medium completely.","[('Narnia', 'GPE')]"
235,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series",What is a book or book series you have been hoping to see turned into a movie or TV series?,[]
236,"Netflix Developing 'The Chronicles of Narnia' Films, TV Series",I hated those books.,[]
237,Prime Thursday night football,Fox apparently. Just saw a station identification brake. ,"[('Fox', 'ORG')]"
238,Prime Thursday night football,I got a commercial for Ted Cruz. No comment.,"[('Ted Cruz', 'PERSON')]"
239,"Do any US streamers watch ""Later..."" (the Jools Holland music show)?","Searching around, I think this airs on MTV Live in the US. You can get that channel via Philo for $20 a month. Includes Cloud DVR, so you can record it if it's not available on-demand.","[('MTV Live', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Philo', 'GPE'), ('20', 'MONEY'), ('Cloud DVR', 'PERSON')]"
240,"Do any US streamers watch ""Later..."" (the Jools Holland music show)?",I used to watch this on HDNet or something. It's a great show.What cable channel is it on?,"[('HDNet', 'ORG')]"
241,"Do any US streamers watch ""Later..."" (the Jools Holland music show)?",I LOVED that show and that was the only thing I missed when I killed DirecTV. Will be following this thread.,[]
242,HDTV Antenna Suggestions!,"Just to clarify, it's a marketing gimmick to call an antenna an 'HDTV antenna.' All TV antennas pull both analog and digital signals from the air. What matters is whether the TV can handle the signal received (e.g., older TVs need a converter box to change the digital signal to analog).  It's why you can buy a house that has a 1970s roof-mounted antenna and use it to watch digital HDTV without modification. (Well, if it's really from the 1970s, you might have to tack a coax jack onto the cable that runs into the house. You used to have to screw down bare wires on the back of a TV.)","[('1970s', 'DATE'), ('the 1970s', 'DATE')]"
243,HDTV Antenna Suggestions!,Are there any antennas Not called HDTV antennas?  It seems every ad I view uses the phrase.   **OP:** Your signals are strong so try the Winegard Flatwave (the black one) http://www.winegard.com/flatwave,"[('the Winegard Flatwave', 'ORG')]"
244,HDTV Antenna Suggestions!,Nailed it. ,[]
245,HDTV Antenna Suggestions!,The wirecutter recently ran a [review series ](https://thewirecutter.com/reviews/best-indoor-hdtv-antenna/)   They’re pretty good usually. ,[]
246,HDTV Antenna Suggestions!,"An omnidirectional antenna rated for 30-40 miles will probably do you best since you have signals coming from two different directions.If that doesn't work well enough though, the more advanced option would be two directional(aka: unidirectional) antennas pointed N/NE and S/SW, plugged into an OTA TV combiner to merge the signals would work too, though you might sacrifice getting channel 39(43.1) that way since it's off on its own in the East.","[('30-40 miles', 'QUANTITY'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('N/NE', 'ORG'), ('S/SW', 'ORG'), ('East', 'LOC')]"
247,HDTV Antenna Suggestions!,"> An omnidirectional antenna rated for 30-40 miles will probably do you best since you have signals coming from two different directions.A directional antenna would be better, since most of his stations are 180 degrees apart.  Some stations will be received on the forward side... others on the rear side.  (That's how my CM4228 is setup.)","[('30-40 miles', 'QUANTITY'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('180 degrees', 'QUANTITY')]"
248,HDTV Antenna Suggestions!,"As already mentioned, you have signals coming from two directions (Dayton, Cincinnati). If you mostly just want the popular networks you could point an antenna towards your stronger/closer signals (Dayton, a bit east of due north). The Dayton direction is particularly convenient as all the popular networks are in the same TV band (UHF). So for an easy install (no adjustment) you could use a boring old 4 bay UHF type antenna pointed northish. Examples:* Digiwave ANT2084, ANT2085* Stellar Labs 30-2426* Solid Signal XS HDB4X AKA Digiwave ANT2086* Channel Master CM4221HD* Antennas Direct DB4eYou will just have to test out the attic. No good way to predict the results.Ref:* https://www.rabbitears.info/market.php?mktid=76* https://www.rabbitears.info/market.php?mktid=40* https://www.fcc.gov/media/engineering/dtvmaps","[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Dayton', 'LOC'), ('Cincinnati', 'GPE'), ('Dayton', 'PERSON'), ('Dayton', 'LOC'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('Digiwave ANT2084', 'PERSON'), ('ANT2085', 'GPE'), ('Stellar', 'GPE'), ('30-2426', 'DATE'), ('Solid Signal XS', 'ORG'), ('Channel Master CM4221HD', 'ORG'), ('Antennas Direct', 'ORG'), ('Ref', 'PERSON')]"
249,HDTV Antenna Suggestions!,"What would be better?  A Stellar Labs 30-2426 or a Digiwave ANT2086/Solid Signal XS HDB4X ?These both seem to be the lower cost option, Both are very close in price and look very similar in specs and design. Does anyone have any experience in one over another? Would it be worth it for the more expensive brands? Thanks for the input!","[(' ', 'ORDINAL'), ('Stellar Labs', 'ORG'), ('30-2426', 'DATE'), ('Digiwave', 'GPE'), ('Signal XS', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
250,Locast NY CBS audio sync way off from video,"Thanks for the heads up! Should be good now, but may drop out of sync again, we will keep an eye on it. We have had to drop a couple of the NY channels for the time being, but are hard at work upgrading our equipment in the market to provide better service, so stay tuned!","[('NY', 'ORG')]"
251,YouTube TV adds support for NBA League Pass w/ $40 add-on channel,For all the basketball fans,[]
252,YouTube TV adds support for NBA League Pass w/ $40 add-on channel,$40! What a great deal! A month! Oh well. :\,"[('40', 'MONEY')]"
253,YouTube TV adds support for NBA League Pass w/ $40 add-on channel,Any option with PlayStation Vue to buy nba league pass? I currently use PlayStation Vue through the Amazon fire,"[('PlayStation Vue', 'PRODUCT'), ('PlayStation Vue', 'PRODUCT'), ('Amazon', 'ORG')]"
254,YouTube TV adds support for NBA League Pass w/ $40 add-on channel,Not at the moment. ,[]
255,YouTube TV adds support for NBA League Pass w/ $40 add-on channel,Sling has NBA League Pass available a la carte for $28.99/month or NBA Team Pass for $17.99/month,"[('Sling', 'ORG'), ('NBA League Pass', 'ORG'), ('28.99/month', 'MONEY'), ('NBA', 'ORG'), ('Team Pass', 'PERSON'), ('17.99/month', 'MONEY')]"
256,YouTube TV adds support for NBA League Pass w/ $40 add-on channel,Has anyone found a way to keep track of scores via the YTTV app? Signed up for League Pass and would rather not have to utilize the NBA app at all. ,"[('NBA', 'ORG')]"
257,YouTube TV adds support for NBA League Pass w/ $40 add-on channel,Use the ESPN app or just Google “NBA” whenever you want the scores?,"[('ESPN', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NBA', 'ORG')]"
258,YouTube TV adds support for NBA League Pass w/ $40 add-on channel,How is this more beneficial than just subscribing to the season pass online? Is the YouTube price discounted?,"[('YouTube', 'ORG')]"
259,YouTube TV adds support for NBA League Pass w/ $40 add-on channel,It's not. In fact it's the cost of the highest tier League Pass package (they offer a team and mid-tier all NBA package for 119 and 199 respectively).I had hoped for a better deal but doesn't surprise me.Also I wish the one team pass was a five team pass like it was originally. ,"[('NBA', 'ORG'), ('119', 'CARDINAL'), ('199', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('five', 'CARDINAL')]"
260,Gizmodo: The Live-Action Star Wars TV Show Is Called The Mandalorian,Don't go breaking my heart🎶,[]
261,Gizmodo: The Live-Action Star Wars TV Show Is Called The Mandalorian,Please be good,[]
262,Gizmodo: The Live-Action Star Wars TV Show Is Called The Mandalorian,"So is everybody from Mandalore a bounty hunter?  They don't do anything else like build roads, open restaurants, et cetera?  Just hunt criminals and collect bounty.","[('Mandalore', 'ORG')]"
263,Why an Antenna Should Be a Part of Your Cord Cutting Setup,"Another one:  Because after initial costs and configuration, it's 100% free to watch TV.  No monthly bills for OTA.","[('100%', 'PERCENT'), ('monthly', 'DATE'), ('OTA', 'ORG')]"
264,Why an Antenna Should Be a Part of Your Cord Cutting Setup,You can get antennas as low as $10 depending on where you live. ,"[('as low as $10', 'MONEY')]"
265,Why an Antenna Should Be a Part of Your Cord Cutting Setup,"One more reason:  OTA doesn’t use data where live streaming does and could potentially push you up against your limit if your internet provider has one.  I usually use my data for on-demand and OTA for live.There are also devices that enable you to broadcast live OTA TV through your wireless router so you can view live TV thru an app on your phone, tablet, Apple TV, Roku, etc.  this will also not count against your data cap since it doesn’t use data. ","[('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('Apple TV', 'ORG'), ('Roku', 'GPE')]"
266,Why an Antenna Should Be a Part of Your Cord Cutting Setup,good Advice.  i definitely want to go this route..  Just need to pick the right OTA DVR ...  *sigh* don't want one with monthly fees lol,"[('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('monthly', 'DATE')]"
267,Why an Antenna Should Be a Part of Your Cord Cutting Setup,"Yes, a cheap OTA TV antenna (as little as $12 last time I checked) is a no-brainer for many people in the USA; but not all. Because the cost can go up dramatically in rural and/or mountainous areas. We live rural. And have a hill directly between us and the nearest broadcast towers, which effectively blocks the signal, so that nobody in our neighborhood has used an antenna for decades.However, back when we badly needed to cut the cord with cable, we took on the challenge. Now we're the first ever to get practical TV here. Around 25 channels. But it cost us around $600, and a ton of research and DIYing. And yeah: we get all the major broadcasters, plus their subsidiary channels. However, most of these channels are just as eaten up with commercials as cable TV. So these days we rarely use them for anything but convenient access to local weather news during storms. There's usually fewer commercials to be seen on free Roku channel alternatives to the antenna TV shows. At present I think we have around 100 free Roku channels (though I personally regularly use only a handful of them).We also have paid Netflix.The article is wrong about no blackouts/outages with antennas. Weather extremes can certainly cause outages. And certain sporting events held locally will be blacked out for us over the antenna. There's also a major local station here that fairly regularly goes down at the source, which is annoying.Of course, cable TV has outages too.Pic quality is often better via antenna than other ways, as the article says. But not always. Since some channels don't do high def. Or show old TV stuff that's low res.As far as OTA 3.0 is concerned, I wouldn't let that be a factor in decisions whatsoever, as I've seen politicians and companies over-promise and under-deliver on new TV and internet options for decades now. OTA 3.0 might amount to nothing at all; or only a worsening, rather than improvement.","[('as little as $12', 'MONEY'), ('USA', 'GPE'), ('decades', 'DATE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('25', 'CARDINAL'), ('around $600', 'MONEY'), ('DIYing', 'ORG'), ('these days', 'DATE'), ('Roku', 'PERSON'), ('around 100', 'CARDINAL'), ('Roku', 'PERSON'), ('Netflix', 'PERSON'), ('OTA 3.0', 'DATE'), ('decades', 'DATE')]"
268,Why an Antenna Should Be a Part of Your Cord Cutting Setup,"> OTA 3.0 might amount to nothing at all; or only a worsening, rather than improvement.This promise has been kept.  It's already being broadcast in several cities, and being rolled-out across the nation with planned completion in Summer 2019.  It upgrades the image from 1080 HD to 2160 Ultra HD..... that's definitely a better image.","[('OTA 3.0', 'DATE'), ('Summer 2019', 'DATE'), ('1080', 'CARDINAL'), ('2160', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ultra', 'NORP')]"
269,Why an Antenna Should Be a Part of Your Cord Cutting Setup,Why not share a coax cable with a few neighbors maybe and make back that money ? ,[]
270,Why an Antenna Should Be a Part of Your Cord Cutting Setup,All those commercials is why an antenna is not part of my cordcutting setup.,[]
271,Why an Antenna Should Be a Part of Your Cord Cutting Setup,"- I skip the commercials with my VCR's fast forward feature.  You'd probably use a DVR... same principle.-  The antenna also carries most of the shows I enjoy watching: New dramas from ABC, CBS, NBC, FOX, CW...... and older dramas from the 1950s, 60s, 70s","[('DVR', 'ORG'), (' ', 'NORP'), ('ABC', 'ORG'), ('CBS', 'ORG'), ('NBC', 'ORG'), ('FOX', 'ORG'), ('CW', 'ORG'), ('the 1950s, 60s, 70s', 'DATE')]"
272,Why an Antenna Should Be a Part of Your Cord Cutting Setup,How do you think broadcasters have the money to keep their transmitters running?,[]
273,Why an Antenna Should Be a Part of Your Cord Cutting Setup,"I mainly use my OTA for local sports because of the picture quality, and the 60hz frame rate.  If you’re not a  sports watcher, I don’t think you really need an antenna that bad. ","[('60hz', 'ORDINAL'), (' ', 'NORP')]"
274,Why an Antenna Should Be a Part of Your Cord Cutting Setup,I do. I'm not paying Vereichzon $80 a month for unlimited data and an MVPD to stream locals over it,"[('Vereichzon', 'ORG'), ('80', 'MONEY'), ('MVPD', 'ORG')]"
275,Why an Antenna Should Be a Part of Your Cord Cutting Setup,"Well, you gotta have an antenna. It’s the basic form of television. You might as well sell your tv if you don’t have an antenna lol ",[]
276,Why an Antenna Should Be a Part of Your Cord Cutting Setup,I have a TV location that only allows an antennae to be laid down or hung directly behind the TV.  Not near a wall or a window.Is there a brand or type of antennae that would work best in that application?Or other ideas?,[]
277,Why an Antenna Should Be a Part of Your Cord Cutting Setup,I am actually in the market for an antenna (I need one by sunday). Any recommended brands? I need an HD antenna to stream the local football games. Thanks in advanced for any assistance.,"[('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('sunday', 'DATE'), ('HD', 'ORG')]"
278,Why an Antenna Should Be a Part of Your Cord Cutting Setup,Read the side panel.  Start a thread and post a TV Fool report for your location.,[]
279,Why an Antenna Should Be a Part of Your Cord Cutting Setup,"my grandparents have a summer cottage in an area with power being the only utility available, so they used OTA for many years, even before it went Digital. they even kept an old TV with an Antenna on it in their actual house, and it's come into use on a few occasions when the Cable provider cuts off the local news channel for stupid reasons.","[('summer', 'DATE'), ('many years', 'DATE'), ('Digital', 'ORG'), ('Antenna', 'PRODUCT'), ('Cable', 'GPE')]"
280,Why an Antenna Should Be a Part of Your Cord Cutting Setup,It already is,[]
281,Why an Antenna Should Be a Part of Your Cord Cutting Setup,I just connected two paper clips to the back of a TV of mine and I got 88 free channels WTF LOL ,"[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('88', 'CARDINAL')]"
282,Why an Antenna Should Be a Part of Your Cord Cutting Setup,"I'm gonna have to disagree with this one. OTA is a regressive technology and looks like shit. Most of us didn't go the route of getting an apple tv, roku, etc., to use exclusively and then have to rely on some dumbass looking antenna sticking out somewhere. Not to mention you have to use the remote on your TV to switch the input.",[]
283,Why an Antenna Should Be a Part of Your Cord Cutting Setup,"> OTA is a regressive technology and looks like shit???.   It's broadcast in 1080 HD and looks better than most streamed HD that is overly compressed/blocky.   Plus within a few months OTA will be upgraded to ATSC 3.0 which features 2160p/ 4K Ultra HD.  How do you define this as ""shit""?  :-o- As for the antenna, a Flatwave or black box is no more ugly than the black box of your Apple tv, roku, etc - http://www.winegard.com/flatwave","[('OTA', 'ORG'), ('1080', 'CARDINAL'), ('a few months OTA', 'DATE'), ('ATSC', 'ORG'), ('2160p/', 'CARDINAL'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), (' ', 'NORP'), ('Flatwave', 'GPE'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
284,Advice on antenna for new house,A medium gain UHF/VHF-high band antenna could work for either location. Examples:* Winegard HD7694P* Channel Master CM-2018,[]
285,Advice on antenna for new house,"By all means put one of these on your roof and aim it East. While it may work in the attic, you'll be glad you have it in the clear during bad weather. ","[('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('East', 'LOC')]"
286,Advice on antenna for new house,> Winegard HD7694PGreat! Thanks for the rec.,"[('Winegard HD7694PGreat', 'PERSON')]"
287,Are we not in a worse situation now?,I don’t feel the need to subscribe to all those services. I have one or two at any given time and am happy as a clam. ,"[('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
288,Are we not in a worse situation now?,"Prime has many other benefits and coupled with Netflix, I’m good to go!","[('Netflix', 'PERSON')]"
289,Are we not in a worse situation now?,"Exactly. The greatest benefit of streaming is allowing you choice to what you want to purchase, rather than being forced to overpay for dozens of channels you don’t want just to get the few you do want. Also, as more content becomes exclusive to different streaming, they are going to have to compete for my business. I will choose what I want based on quality and price. I’m not going to get every service, so they better compete hard by making a great product at an affordable price or I won’t subscribe. ","[('dozens', 'CARDINAL')]"
290,Are we not in a worse situation now?,Yes and you can change which you are using from time to time to catch up on things that are exclusive if you want to see it.,[]
291,Are we not in a worse situation now?,I agree with that plus the fact that you can cancel at anytime without having to do anything.  No having to call customer support and have them keep transferring you instead of canceling you.  No set top box that you have to turn in and then they say that you never turned it in.  ,[]
292,Are we not in a worse situation now?,"I look at it like the 4 broadcast. I used to have faith that Fox was going to put up good action shows and animated. NBC does good drama and sit coms. And ABC has some good comedy. And CBS is just good for football. Netflix produces reliable quality material. Prime has some hits and misses, but you can expand it with the premium channels. Hulu has some reliable streams but rarely full seasons that you can’t find anywhere else. And YouTube, Facebook, and presumably apple’s material is all amateurish. So make concessions, you only need one or two to be satisfied. Any more is just hedonism. Lol","[('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('Fox', 'PERSON'), ('NBC', 'ORG'), ('ABC', 'ORG'), ('CBS', 'ORG'), ('Netflix', 'PERSON'), ('Hulu', 'GPE'), ('YouTube', 'NORP'), ('Facebook', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Lol', 'PERSON')]"
293,Are we not in a worse situation now?,"The question becomes how much you're actually saving by limiting your content consumption versus what it would cost to have it all through cable.I found that with YouTube TV and Netflix alone (in addition to standalone internet service provided by my cable company) my total monthly bill was pretty close to what I'd been paying before I cut the cord.  Adding a third service would have pushed it over the top.  Ultimately I choose to remain a cord cutter because I prefer cloud DVR to traditional DVR, but otherwise I would probably just be happier with cable, and my spending would be about the same despite having access to a lot more content.","[('YouTube TV', 'ORG'), ('Netflix', 'PERSON'), ('third', 'ORDINAL'), ('DVR', 'ORG'), ('DVR', 'ORG')]"
294,Are we not in a worse situation now?,"This. Why do people feel that they have to have everything? If you need to see it all, just rotate services every few months. With the way things are, you have the option of spending a varying amount. Before, it was pay a lot all the time. ","[('every few months', 'DATE')]"
295,Are we not in a worse situation now?,"Many people were still paying high cable bills while being subscribed to a few of those services, so there are savings. If having all the same channel coverage is important to you, then maybe cord cutting isn’t your solution. Gotta take inventory of your viewing habits and decide if there are sacrifices you can make. We’ll never get a la carte channels because things are always packaged, but I do love not having 100 sports channels in my guide and foreign language networks overcharging me for their programming. ","[('100', 'CARDINAL')]"
296,Are we not in a worse situation now?,"Ha, 100 sports networks are the one thing I miss from cable. I've never felt like I'm missing something until I try to watch football only to find out my team is playing on ESPN this week.","[('100', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('ESPN', 'ORG'), ('this week', 'DATE')]"
